Don't lay a finger on those
dice, Josuke Higashikata!
I would stay put if I were you.
I wonder what he's gonna do if he finds
out I've been cheating this whole time.
Well, let's just say a simple apology
won't be enough to smooth things over.
What exactly is the problem?
It might be my mind playing tricks, but
I could swear the dice are staring at me.
Well, at any rate, let's
get back to the game.
Wow, you're way braver than I am.
It'll just be two for me.
Catch my drift now, Mr. Alien?
I know the point is to come out on top,
but I only have to do that by a little bit.
All right, go!
It's like what I'm saying is going
in one ear and out the other!
Guess that's what you
call a streak of luck, eh?
Rolling that score again isn't impossible.
An omen is worth five
times the initial bet, yes?
Here you go.
The dice will roll as they may.
Guess so.
You can never predict these
kinds of things, am I right?
Let's break down, break down.
Break down, break down.
Let's go.
Meguru yuki de ikiru Match...
Nakedos!
You're insufferable.
However, for Mr.
Joestar and Koichi's sakes, I've been
keeping my cool where you're concerned.
But that ends now.
Cheating me crosses every line ever drawn.
I'm sure you've been gloating this entire
time, and the thought of it makes me sick.
Just give me your hands.
I'll have Shining Diamond fix it for you.
Shut your mouth!
Do you have any idea why I
did that to my little finger?
So you can't back out of the game
like a coward, Josuke Higashkata!
You're just a pea-brained dullard.
I refuse to let you
disrespect the Great Rohan!
Each of us is going to have one more turn.
And as we play, I'll find a way to
see through your immoral deceptions.
But if I fail to uncover the truth
behind your clandestine tactics,
here's two million yen.
Consider it monetary incentive to receive
treatment from Shining
Diamond after the game.
However, if I do unveil the
nature of your deception,
Your little finger will belong
to me, Josuke Higashikata.
Hey!
Looks like you two are having
a rip-snortin' good time!
Yo! Josuke! What's up?
Long time no see.
I've been stuck in that stupid
hospital for a month now.
I'm still kind of fuzzy on the details,
but I'm told I conked my
noggin on the side of the road.
Tamami?
What the heck are you poking
your nose around here for?
I hired him to be a repo man
of sorts, just as a precaution.
Repo man?
Sorry to keep you boys waiting,
but I'm here and ready to serve.
And not to worry, I'm prepared.
My trusty solar fixing lock will
ensure you receive what we agreed on.
I will fulfill my duty regardless of
who the victor is, you have my word.
My fees, whichever is the
greatest, Quee or 20%.
You'll both play one more round,
while Rohan tries to figure out how
you're cheating him, isn't that right?
Yes.
What?!
Although,
there's a chance you could be
tempted to withhold your trick,
so I will simply ensure that you don't.
Should you win without
your usual deceptions,
Tamami's lock will activate and
automatically attach itself to your body.
Now I'm really up shit creek.
It's now or never.
I've got to pull off this trick
and get myself out of this mess
If we're clear, I'll roll first.
Get ready
Here it comes
A four!
Two threes and a four
Thank God a normal result for once.
He won't figure it out now
So, it's my turn now, right?
Seems like a weight's been
lifted off your shoulders.
It's almost as though a task you
requested if someone was a success.
Just stay calm.
Rohan still doesn't have a clue.
I can do this.
What in the...
Is that barf?
Oh shit, he's getting dizzy.
I bet it's because Rohan
was shaking him so much.
Not so fast.
I insist you stop covering the dice.
I can't see them if they're
in your hand like that.
Shake the dice with your palm open.
Huh?
Must be a fire somewhere.
What?
Sirens?
That's right.
He's allergic to the sound of sirens.
At this rate, he'll revert back to normal.
What is the hold-up?
Quit your stalling!
Show me what you're holding in your hand!
Aaaaaaah!
You just heard the way I get
myself hyped up for battle!
Now get ready to lose!
Do it! Go!
It's a 6-6-6 Hamon!
And the lock didn't activate!
Josuke's a low-down rotten cheater!
So how about it?
Did you figure it out, Rohan-sensei?
Well, what's the word?
Does your silence mean
you throw it in the towel?
Looks like those weird little
dots aren't on Rohan's side.
Hang in there.
Oh, don't leave us here in suspense!
Did you figure it out or not?
Of course it all makes sense
Damn, I'm toast I've got it!
The fire's here!
Rohan Sensei, your house
is burning to the ground.
It was the magnifying glass.
The sunlight went through
it and started the fire.
We were distracted and didn't notice.
Shut up!
I don't care if the house
ends up in a heap of ash All
that matters here is figuring
out how Josuke's cheating!
Don't be ridiculous!
Just take your two million
and get the hell out of here!
Well, I think I'll be going now.
Hey, come back!
But before I go, I'll
fix that finger of yours!
Oh, you can't just heal
people without permission!
Josuke, wait!
You bastard!
That was a close one.
I guess I'm the kind of guy that
some people just love to hate, huh?
Who would've figured?
What's wrong?
You seem displeased.
Tell me, was I of adequate
assistance to you?
Could you like... Shut up! Jeez!
Rohan Kishibe's house.
Half burned and seven
million yen in fire damage.
Josuke may have escaped unscathed,
but he managed to find himself
even further on Rohan's bad side.
Just a friendly reminder
to all you drivers out
there to be extra careful
when you're on the road.
It seems a motorcycle crashed at the
entrance of Futatsumori Tunnel yesterday,
and the young rider was badly injured.
Police later discovered
that the accident...
Mom's been acting different lately.
She's been dressing up,
wearing new lipstick.
She's happy.
Did something happen?
Interesting mom doesn't usually get
naked in front of dad not in that way.
Sometimes I wonder if I was born to
parents with no love for each other.
What's he doing?
Josuke, the guy's guitar, Jotaro, Kujo,
they're the reason I'm in this predicament.
Oh, Josuke, it's you.
Thank you again.
Hey man, no problem.
So did you find a place to
sleep and get a bite to eat?
Mikitaka! Mikitaka!
Get your hiney over here this instant!
We haven't been in town that long,
and there are lots of errands
to be done, young man.
Of course. Sorry, Mother.
I'm coming. Huh? Mother?
Oh, for Pete's sake.
Are you telling people
that you're an alien again?
What have I told you about
playing these pranks?
I do apologize if my
boy has been a bother.
They actually took him seriously
at his school in Tokyo.
You should have seen the ruckus he caused.
Now, if you'll excuse us.
What?
I brainwashed her, isn't that great?
As far as she knows, I'm her son.
Mikitaka Hazekura is my alias
while I'm here on Earth.
So long for now.
Mikitaka, it's time to go!
What the hell is going on here?
Just who the devil was that armball?
Was he serious about being an alien?
Or was he simply a stand user I created
when I threw the arrow and cut his neck?
The way that boy was able
to drive a wedge between
Josuke and Rohan was
certainly a sight of the hold.
But, he's out.
Next they'll face the stand, Highway Kick.
It'll crush whoever hunts my son.
Are you just going to ignore me?
The least you could do is say hello.
It's common courtesy to address those
older than you, Josuke Higashikata.
Sorry about yesterday.
So, uh, that fire was
crazy, wasn't it? Yes.
That was approximately 2.5
million yen worth of furniture.
Those pieces were used in the
movie Pretty Woman, you know.
Not that any of that bothers me.
What?
Have a seat.
Mark my words, I'll repay you for
yesterday's game one way or another.
That was...
Josuke, did you see that?
There was a door to a
house in the tunnel wall.
Someone's inside.
It's a window.
There's a room beyond these tunnel walls.
And from what I can see,
someone's living in it.
There's a man, too.
But I can't see their faces.
What is he attempting to do?
Josuke, tell me you saw that. Enough!
I've had it with you.
Don't think you can screw with me forever.
No one else can see the room.
Is that house a new stand user?
The man who cut off that woman's
hand, could he be Yoshikage Kira?
You expect me to believe there
was a room inside the tunnel?
You're not fooling anyone.
Is that half-baked lie your
way of getting back at me?
So you have no faith in me.
Is that what you're saying?
That's rich coming from
a cheater like you.
And not only are you a cheater, you're
a cheater who lies to cover his tracks.
You have the gall to accuse me of lying?
Well, I should have known we
would never see eye to eye.
You wouldn't understand even if
I took you back there to see it.
All right, let's do this.
The exit...
There's nothing here.
I could have sworn there was
something, but it's just a wall.
So it was an illusion.
What?
Wait, this is...
It's the room I saw from the bus.
He just appeared out of thin air.
But what happened to the man
and woman who were in here?
Blast it!
Something's in there!
This room is a trap and I fell for it!
Whatever's in there is getting closer.
I don't see a thing,
but something is coming!
that wouldn't have ended
well it was totally
invisible but something was moving toward
me something non-human that room was bait
and the cure-looking Fool was an illusion
there's no doubt in my
mind that room is a stand
going it alone is risky
i should tell mr joestar
Damn it!
It's still coming?
What the hell?
They look just like living footprints!
Are they the stand?
How are they so fast?
I got away, so it can't run faster
than 60 kilometers per hour.
It's a long-range stand.
What?
It caught up to me, but I only
lowered my speed by a fraction.
Shit.
I'll make it a book and take
control with Heaven's Door.
It's sopping my strength.
I was hoping I'd never have to see
Rohan's smug face again, but here I am.
He may think I'm a dumb liar, but
he'll see that I have a heart too.
Now where the heck is that guy?
What?
Is that Rohan's motorcycle?
Why'd it just fly out of the tunnel?
And where's Rohan?
It's a monster!
Utterly delectable!
You shall become my nourishment!
Heaven! Heaven's door!
This stand's name is Highway Kick.
That room was his trap.
It hunts down anyone who enters the room.
Then it pursues them like a rabid dog.
When it finally catches them, it
drains them of all their nutrients.
If Highway Kick is able to touch
you, its weakness disappears?
That's crazy!
It's no use.
My strength is fading.
I can't even read.
He's depleting more and
more of my strength.
Raiding in a command is impossible now.
What? Now?
Rohan!
Hey! Rohan! You here?
Josuke, you actually came back?
You have a friend. How nice.
Rohan, I believe he said.
hey Rohan answer me come
on Rohan wait
is that what
the Rohan well go ahead
call your friend over so he
can rescue you shout out
for help do it there's
nothing stopping you I've
left a fraction of your body's
nutrients behind if you
agree to call out for his
assistance i might be kind
enough to spare your life i'll
simply go after him instead
of sucking you dry now then
why don't you make this easy
for everyone and lure him
into the room you want to
live don't you all you need
to do is get him to walk
inside what the hell is this
place if i didn't know any
better i'd say someone lives
here hurry and open your
mouth before it's too late
if you don't act now he's
likely to walk away it's
not as if you two actually
care about each other right
last chance ask him to save
you maybe you want to die
if if i bait him into coming
if i hand him over to you
will will you really keep your promise and
spare my life i need to
hear you say the words
but of course i give you my word if
you hold up your end of our arrangement
no harm will come to you now speak
bring me my meal sorry but i refuse
what you should know that one of rohan
kishibe's favorite pastimes is saying
no to fools who think they're tough
shit so i'm afraid your meal's been
canceled.
Josuke, run!
No matter what happens, you
can't come in this room.
If you do, you're
dead!
You bastard!
You really don't know me at all, do you?
I'm not one to sit back
and do as I'm told.
Now let me at this dickwad.
His ass is grass.
Tell me where he's hiding and I'll get to
Work, what didn't you
hear a single word I said?
You have to escape!
I just told you he's deadly.
You always do the exact
opposite of what I'm thinking.
That's why I despise you
with a burning passion!
That's why you bugged the out of me!
He's going to attack you, fool!
You've already let him
grab hold of your scent!
At last time to eat heaven's door?
Njousuke,
Highway Kick will follow you anywhere
at a speed of 60 kilometers per hour.
You have to find the user.
Your only way out of this predicament
is to defeat the thing's user.
You just don't shut up, do you?
It's a bad habit.
Rohan!
I can't believe it.
Rohan went out of his way to save me.
It's weird.
I'm getting all choked up over it.
That guy's alright.
Leave it to me, Rohan.
You said all I had to
do was find its user.
But I'll do much more than that.
I'm gonna pummel his soul-sucking ass.
Hang in there, Rohan!
Any time I need to see your
face it has closed my eyes.
And I am taken to a place
where you're crystal mine.
I'm a gentle feeling.
Take a shelter in the face of my spine.
Straight like a Chaka cherry cola.
I don't need to try to explain.
I just hold on tight.
And if it happens again?
I'ma move so slightly To the arms and
the lips and the face To the humic
and the ball that I need to I want to
Come and stand a little bit closer.
Breathe in and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what
hit you When I get to you.
Ooh, I want you.
I don't know if I need you.
But ooh, I got it by now.
Ooh, I want you.
I don't know if I need you.
But ooh, I got it by now.